<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Upcoming on BSA Troop 222</title><link>https://troop222Site.github.io/tags/upcoming/</link><description>Recent content in Upcoming on BSA Troop 222</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://troop222Site.github.io/tags/upcoming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Upcoming Antietam Trip</title><link>https://troop222Site.github.io/p/upcoming-antietam-trip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://troop222Site.github.io/p/upcoming-antietam-trip/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://troop222Site.github.io/p/upcoming-antietam-trip/cover.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Upcoming Antietam Trip" />&lt;h1 id="description">Description&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Troop 222 visits Antietam National Battlefield Join us as we camp on and tour this historic Civil War battlefield and learn about its history. This trip include a guided tour of the battlefield and camping at a Scouts only campsite on the battlefield grounds. Antietam National Battlefield is the site of the bloodiest one day battle in American history. After twelve hours of savage combat on September 17, 1862, 23,000 soldiers were killed, wounded or missing. The Battle of Antietam ended the Confederate Army of Northern Virginia&amp;rsquo;s first invasion into the North and led to Abraham Lincoln&amp;rsquo;s issuance of the preliminary Emancipation Proclamation.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="details">Details&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>When:&lt;/strong> 11/10/23 to 11/12/23&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Where:&lt;/strong> Antietam National Battlefield, The Rohrbach Campground site 007, 5831 Dunker Church Rd, Sharpsburg 21782&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Departure:&lt;/strong> 6PM on 11/10/23 at Advent Lutheran&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Return:&lt;/strong> Noon on 11/12/23 at Advent Lutheran&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Weather:&lt;/strong> Highs of 50F lows of 30F&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="important-notice">Important Notice&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>We welcome ALL interested attendees on our trips&amp;ndash;HOWEVER clearances are necessary. ALL TRIP-GOERS (scouts, siblings, adults, friends) must have a health form Part A and B on file with the troop. ALL ADULTS must have YPT and clearances and be registered leaders as outlined above. ALL SCOUTS AND YOUTH must have signed permission slips. The following forms must be completed and given to a troop leader no later than Friday night of the trip at 5:30pm:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>BSA Permission Slip – For every scout and person under 18 attending, this must be completed, signed and turned into a troop leader before the troop departs. This form is generated using the &amp;ldquo;Permission Slip&amp;rdquo; button toward the bottom of the event page in Scoutbook.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>BSA Medical Form (Parts A &amp;amp; B) – You only need to submit this if you did not already submit this, this summer or this Scout year. Otherwise this must be completed, signed and turned in to a Troop leader before the Troop departs. All adults attending need these forms on file as well. This is available on the BSA website at &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.scouting.org/health-and-safety/ahmr/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://www.scouting.org/health-and-safety/ahmr/&lt;/a> under All Scouting Events.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Youth Protection Training – It is BSA policy that ALL adults attending any trip ARE REGISTERED LEADERS and complete the BSA Youth Protection Training - this is a 50 minute on-line training course. Go to &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.scouting.org/...rotection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://www.scouting.org/...rotection/&lt;/a> and follow the link, &amp;ldquo;Click here to login and take Youth Protection training&amp;rdquo;. After selecting the link, you will need to create an account for MyScouting.org if you don’t have one. Please note that Chester County Council is adding additional requirements including background checks on all adult volunteers to comply with State Law – See the Chester County Council website or contact an adult leader.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>If you have any questions, please feel free to speak with a troop adult leader at a Monday meeting or contact me via the contact info below.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>